Do you pick it up or do you leave it?
>> It looks like a grave.
>> What? Okay, can you tell she's from
Florida?
>> that?
>> Oh, I don't know. I mean, it's not
necessarily a grave.
>> What would you call that?
>> That's a piece of concrete.
>> In the shape of a grave?
>> It does kind of look like this block was
laid on there. What? Now I'm curious.
>> It's being like a structure that was
there.
>> Oh.
This block right here?
>> What kind of structure is that shape?
>> That is a fair question. Look at every
other rock around here. But you're
right, like what the hell is it? Like it
didn't just show up. Kind of how you
know the earth didn't happen from a big
bang theory. Stuff don't just show up.
Do we pick it up?
>> Okay, so what is it? Is it a grave?
>> What if it's just dirt underneath there?
I don't think it's a grave.
>> What is it?
>> I mean, it seems to
it could be like a wall slab.
>> Where's the rest of the wall?
>> I mean, it could be that somebody just
put it here.
>> It takes a great deal of effort to move
this piece of rock right here, don't it?
Do you pick it up or do you leave it?